Guide to the David Low Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1915-85; Series I; 6.25; (15 boxes)
  - PERSONAL
    - Cudlipp, Percy, 1953 Dec 14 (Box 1, Folder 55)
      See also: Express Newspapers, Box 6, folders 293-97 and Daily Herald, Box 6, folder 288
    - Cummings, Arthur J., 1934-38 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - "D" general, 1927-62, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Dalton, Hugh, 1942-48 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Davis, Clement, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Dearden, Harold, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Driberg, Thomas E. N., 1953 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Drinkwater, John, 1928-38 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Dyson, Bill, 1919-36 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - "E" general, 1921-1956 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Eccles, David, 1949-53 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Edelman, Maurice, 1954, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Eden, Anthony, 1945-54 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Edwards, Philip, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Einzig, Paul, 1944 Jan 16 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Eliot, T. S., 1945-57, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Elliot, Walter, 1933-49 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - "F" general, 1930-56, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Fanshaw, Evelyn, 1943 Mar 2 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Fearon, Percy ("Poy"), 1925-34 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Ferrer, José, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Foot, Michael, 1962 Apr 18 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Freud, Sigmund, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Freud, Ernst L., 1956 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - "G" general, 1923-62, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Gaitskell, Hugh, 1957 Sep 16 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Gielgud, John, ca. 1939-45 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Gifford, Lord, 1937-38 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Gollancz, Victor and Ruth, 1941-61 (Box 2, Folder 82)
      See also: Victor Gollancz, Ltd., Box 8, folder 367
    - Gordon-Walker, Patrick C., 1963 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Green, Allin, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Guinness, Alec, 1949 Aug 18 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Gunter, Ray, 1962 Feb 12 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - "H" general, 1921-62, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 87-89)
    - Haley, W. J., 1949-55 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Hammarsköjld, Dag, 1958-60 (Box 2, Folder 91)
      See also: United Nations, Box 9, folder 450
    - Harker-Thomas, Grace, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Harris, H. Wilson, 1930-33 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Hart-Davis, Rupert, 1949-63 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Hauge, Gabriel, 1953 Oct 22 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Henderson, J. F., 1936-37 (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Hess, Myra, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Hill, Raven, 1930-31 (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Hiscocks, Fred, 1937-38 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Hogg, Douglas McGarel, Viscount Hailsham, 1954-57, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Holtby, Winifred, 1928-29 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Hopkinson, Henry, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Hore-Belisha, Leslie, 1938, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - Horrabin, J. Frank, 1921-61 (Box 2, Folder 104-05)
    - Houston, Lucy, 1934-37, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - Houston, Renée, 1929 Feb 11 (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - Huddleston, Sisley, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - Hughes, Emrys, 1937-62, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Huxley, Aldous, 1933-56 (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - Huxley, Julian, Sir, 1935-57 (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - "I" general, 1937-50, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - "J" general, 1929-62 (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - Joad, Cyril E. M., 1930-45 (Box 2, Folder 114)
    - Joynson-Hicks, William, Sir ("Jix"), 1925-33 (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - "K" general, 1926-59, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - Karsh, Yousef, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Keir, David Lindsay, Sir, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Kelly, Gerald, 1934-53 (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Kennedy, Joseph P., 1939 Nov 9 (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - Kenworthy, J. M., 1924-28 (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - Keynes, John Maynard, 1933-56, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - King-Hall, Stephen, 1933-45 (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Kipling, Rudyard, 1926 Sep 2 (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - Koestler, Arthur, 1955-60 (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - Korda, Alexander (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - "L" general, 1924-63, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 127-29)
    - Laemmle, Carl, 1938 Dec 10 (Box 3, Folder 130)
    - Laski, Harold J., 1933-56 (Box 3, Folder 131)
    - Lawson, J. J., 1933-34 (Box 3, Folder 132)
    - Lee, Roy S., 1953-56 (Box 3, Folder 133)
    - Lewis, Wyndham, 1932-48, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 134)
    - Liddell Hart, B. H., 1938-55 (Box 3, Folder 135)
    - Lion, Leon M., 1936-38 (Box 3, Folder 136)
    - Locker Lampson, Oliver, 1923-41 (Box 3, Folder 137)
    - Longden, Gilbert, 1959 Mar 18 (Box 3, Folder 138)
    - Lora [?] Force [?], G., 1943-44 (Box 3, Folder 139)
    - Lorant, Stefan, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 140)
      See also: Lilliput, Box 7, folder 322 and Picture Post, Box 8, folder 347
    - "M" general, 1920-63, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 141-43)
    - Macaulay, Rose, 1934-42, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 144)
    - MacColl, D. S., 1938-40 (Box 3, Folder 145)
    - MacDonald, J. Ramsay, 1923-35 (Box 3, Folder 146)
    - McIntosh, Hugh D., 1927-29 (Box 3, Folder 147)
    - Mackay, R. W. G., 1947 Jul 2 (Box 3, Folder 148)
    - Mackenzie Livingstone, A., 1925 Feb 16 (Box 3, Folder 149)
    - MacLaren, Andrew M., 1927-51, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 150)
    - Macmillan, Harold, 1953 Dec 30 (Box 3, Folder 151)
    - Mallon, J. J., 1930-60, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 152)
    - Mander, Geoffrey Le M., 1938, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 153)
    - Mandling, R., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 154)
    - Mannin, Ethel, 1934-36 (Box 3, Folder 155)
    - Marples, Ernest, 1958, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 156)
    - Marrett [?], G. H., 1927 Dec 8 (Box 3, Folder 157)
    - Maugham, W. Somerset, 1933 Sep 13 (Box 3, Folder 158)
    - Maxton, James, 1933 May 17 (Box 3, Folder 159)
    - Mikardo, Ian, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 160)
    - Milne, A. A., 1932-35, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 161)
    - Mitchison, Naomi, 1937, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 162)
    - Moffett, T. H., 1937 (Box 3, Folder 163)
    - Mond, Alfred Moritz, Baron Melchett, 1929-37 (Box 3, Folder 164)
    - Morrison, Herbert, 1931-62 (Box 3, Folder 165-66)
    - Morrison, W. S., 1958 Mar 28 (Box 3, Folder 167)
    - Mountbatten, Louis Francis Albert Victor Nicholas, first Earl of Montbatten, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 168)
    - Moynihan, Lord, 1933, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 169)
    - Muggeridge, Malcolm, 1953-56 (Box 3, Folder 170)
    - Murray, Gilbert, 1937-56 (Box 3, Folder 171)
    - "N" general, 1927-60, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 172-74)
    - Ney, Marie, 1937-61, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 175)
    - Nicholson, Godfrey, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 176)
    - Noel-Baker, Philip, 1934-56 (Box 4, Folder 177)
    - Northern Ireland, Government of, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 178)
    - Northwood, E. P.
      See: Northern Ireland, Government of, Box 4, folder 178
    - Norton, Clifford, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 179)
    - "O" general, 1926-63, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 180)
    - "P" general, 1929-54, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 181-83)
    - Pares, Bernard, 1938-41 (Box 4, Folder 184)
    - Parkhurst, E. Sylvia, 1935-48 (Box 4, Folder 185)
    - Partridge, Bernard, 1928 Jul 1 (Box 4, Folder 186)
    - Phillips, Marion [?], 1930 Nov 11 (Box 4, Folder 187)
    - Pick, F. W., 1937-39 (Box 4, Folder 188)
    - Pick, Frank, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 189)
    - Platts-Mills [?], John, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 190)
    - Pollitt, Harry, 1929-36 (Box 4, Folder 191)
    - Potter, Stephen, 1943-58 (Box 4, Folder 192)
    - Preston, Harry, 1927-36 (Box 4, Folder 193)
    - Priestley, J. B., 1933-50, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 194)
    - Pritt, D. N., 1935-38 (Box 4, Folder 195)
    - "R" general, 1927-63, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 196-97)
    - Rathbone, Eleanor Florence, 1937 Oct 27 (Box 4, Folder 198)
    - Reinhardt, Max, 1959, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 199)
    - Rhondda, Margaret Haig (Thomas) Mackworth, viscountess, 1929-33 (Box 4, Folder 200)
    - Richards, Grant, 1929-36 (Box 4, Folder 201)
    - Richardson, Norah, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 202)
    - Riddell, Lord, 1928 (Box 4, Folder 203)
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1948 Jul 17 (Box 4, Folder 204)
    - Rosenwald, Lessing J., 1941 (Box 4, Folder 205)
    - Rothenstein, John, 1944-54 (Box 4, Folder 206)
    - Rothenstein, John (Mrs.), n.d. (Box 4, Folder 207)
    - Rothenstein, William, Sir, 1929-45, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 208)
    - Rothschild, Lord, 1937-38 (Box 4, Folder 209)
    - Russell, Bertrand, 1933, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 210)
    - Russell, Leonard, 1936-37 (Box 4, Folder 211)
    - "S" general, 1924-63, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 212-14)
    - Scott, J. W. Robertson, 1944-52, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 215)
    - Shaw, George Bernard, 1921, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 216)
    - Shinwell, E., 1945 Nov 13 (Box 5, Folder 217)
    - Simon, Lord, 1949-50 (Box 5, Folder 218)
    - Sinclair, Upton, 1957 May 18 (Box 5, Folder 219)
    - Snowden, Philip, 1925-35 (Box 5, Folder 220)
    - Soskice, Frank, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 221)
    - Spring, Howard, 1933-45 (Box 5, Folder 222)
    - Stopes, Marie C., 1930-49 (Box 5, Folder 223)
    - Strabolgi, Lord, 1934-36, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 224)
    - Streicher, Lawrence H., 1961-62 (Box 5, Folder 225)
    - Streit, Clarence and Jeanne, 1938-57 (Box 5, Folder 226)
    - Strong, L. A. G., 1936-52 (Box 5, Folder 227)
    - Strube, George, 1929-48 (Box 5, Folder 228)
    - Summerskill, Edith, 1945-55 (Box 5, Folder 229)
    - Swaffer, Hannen, 1925-50 (Box 5, Folder 230)
    - Symons, A. J. A., 1937 (Box 5, Folder 231)
    - "T" general, 1926-63, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 232)
    - Tate Gallery
      See: John Rothenstein, Box 4, folder 206
    - Terhune, A. M., 1936-56 (Box 5, Folder 233)
    - Thomas, F. W., 1942-56, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 234)
    - Thomas, J. H., 1926-33 (Box 5, Folder 235)
    - Thompson, Edward, 1942-44 (Box 5, Folder 236)
    - Thorogood, Horace, 1935-60, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 237)
    - Toynbee Hall
      See: J. J. Mallon, Box 3, folder 152
    - "U" general, 1937-56 (Box 5, Folder 238)
    - "V" general, 1933-62, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 239)
    - "W" general, 1921-61, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 240-242)
    - Wade, Arthur S., 1937-38 (Box 5, Folder 243)
    - Ward, Fannie, 1927, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 244)
    - Waugh, Alec, 1935-47 (Box 5, Folder 245)
    - Waugh, Evelyn, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 246)
    - Wedgwood, Josiah C., 1922-40 (Box 5, Folder 247)
    - Weiss, Victor ("Vicky"), 1958-59 (Box 5, Folder 248)
    - Weizman, Chaim, 1945, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 249)
    - Wells, Catherine, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 250)
    - Wells, Gip, 1956-57, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 251)
    - Wells, H. G., 1926-46, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 252-53)
    - Wells, Marjorie, 1956 Mar 16 (Box 5, Folder 254)
    - West, Anthony, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 255)
    - West, Rebecca, 1933-46, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 256)
    - Wheatley, Dennis, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 257)
    - Wigg, G. E. C., 1946 Dec 5 (Box 5, Folder 258)
    - Wilkinson, Ellen, 1942, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 259)
    - Williams, Herbert G., 1943 Sep 13 (Box 5, Folder 260)
    - Wilson, Harold, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 261)
    - Wodehouse, P. G., 1933 (Box 5, Folder 262)
    - Woolf, Leonard, 1937 Mar 12 (Box 5, Folder 263)
    - Woolton, Lord, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 264)
    - Wyllie, J., n.d. (Box 5, Folder 265)
    - "Y" general, 1928-63 (Box 5, Folder 266)
    - Young, George R., 1954 (Box 5, Folder 267)
    - Unidentified, 1927-48, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 268)
  - PROFESSIONAL
    - "A" general, 1933-57 (Box 6, Folder 269)
    - Aitken, William
      See: Express Newspapers, Box 6, folders 293-97
    - "B" general, 1938-45 (Box 6, Folder 270)
    - Bader, E.
      See: Scott Bader Commonwealth Limited, Box 8, folder 354
    - Baily, Leslie, 1958-59 (Box 6, Folder 271)
      See also: The British Broadcasting Corporation, Box 6, folders 275-77
    - Beaverbrook, Max Aitken Lord, 1923-63 (Box 6, Folder 272-74)
    - Blackburn, T.
    - Bone, James
      See: Manchester Guardian, Box 7, folders 325-28
    - Boswell, Ronald
      See: The British Broadcasting Corporation, Box 6, folders 275-77
    - Bradshaw, Percy V.
      See: Milford House, Box 7, folder 331
    - The British Broadcasting Corporation, 1936-57 (Box 6, Folder 275-77)
    - The British Film Institute, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 278)
    - British Museum: Department of Prints and Drawings, 1934 (Box 6, Folder 279)
    - Byard, Theodore
      See: William Heinemann, Ltd., Box 8, folder 370
    - "C" general, 1936-59, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 280)
    - Cadbury, Henry T.
      See: Cadbury Press, Box 6, folder 281
    - Cadbury Press, 1920-49 (Box 6, Folder 281)
    - Cape, Jonathan
      See: Jonathan Cape Limited, Box 7, folder 319
    - The Cartoonists Club, 1962-63 (Box 6, Folder 282)
      See also: Speeches, Box 21, folder 979 and Honors, Box 25, folder 1073
    - Castlerosse, Valentine
    - Christiansen, A.
    - Citrine, Walter M.
      See: The Trades Union Congress General Council, Box 8, folder 364
    - The Civil Service Clerical Association, 1938-41 (Box 6, Folder 283)
    - Clarkson, Anthony
      See: Illustrated, Box 7, folder 315
    - Clifford Bloxham and Partners Limited, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 284)
    - Common Ground, 1948-55 (Box 6, Folder 285)
    - Communist Party of Great Britain, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 286)
    - Cowen, Charles
    - Cudlipp, Percy
      See: Personal Correspondence, Box 1, folder 55; Express Newspapers, Box 6, folders 293-97; and Daily Herald, Box 6, folder 288
    - "D" general, 1938-55 (Box 6, Folder 287)
    - Daily Herald, 1926-50 (Box 6, Folder 288)
    - Daily News
    - Daley, S. D., 1940 Jun 28 (Box 6, Folder 289)
    - Dancy, Eric B.
      See: Intercontinental Press, Box 7, folder 317
    - "E" general, 1948-53 (Box 6, Folder 290)
    - Empire Exhibition, Scotland--1938 (Box 6, Folder 291)
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica, 1953-63 (Box 6, Folder 292)
    - Express Newspapers, 1928-54, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 293-97)
    - "F" general, 1933-46 (Box 6, Folder 298)
    - Fay, Gerard
    - Federn, Helene, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 299)
    - First British Artists Congress & 1937 Exhibition (Box 6, Folder 300)
    - Fothergill, H. Senior, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 301)
    - "G" general, 1928-38 (Box 6, Folder 302)
    - Gaspar, Imre
      See: Gasparcolor Limited, Box 6, folders 303-04
    - Gasparcolor Limited: Correspondence, 1935-37 (Box 6, Folder 303)
    - Gasparcolor Limited: Programs, cartoon sketches, ideas, ca. 1936-37 (Box 6, Folder 304)
    - Gilbert, G.
    - Gollancz, Victor
      See: Victor Gollancz, Ltd., Box 8, folder 367
    - Great Britain
      - Central Office of Information, 1949-58 (Box 6, Folder 305)
      - Foreign Office
        - American Information Department, 1946 Sep 14 (Box 6, Folder 306)
        - Political Intelligence Department, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 307)
        - Ministry of Information, 1942-46 (Box 6, Folder 308)
    - Guedalla, Philip, 1924-56 (Box 6, Folder 309)
    - Gunn, Herbert
    - "H" general, 1936-56 (Box 7, Folder 310)
    - Hamilton, Hamish
      See: Hamish Hamilton Ltd., Box 7, folder 311
    - Hamish Hamilton Ltd., 1937-38 (Box 7, Folder 311)
    - Hetherington, Alastair
    - Hinden, Rita
      See: Socialist Commentary, Box 8, folder 357
    - Hjemmet, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 312)
    - Hollowood, Bernard
      See: Punch, Box 8, folder 349
    - House of Commons: Press Gallery Trust, 1937 Dec 8 (Box 7, Folder 313)
    - "I" general, 1937-52 (Box 7, Folder 314)
    - Illustrated, 1954-55 (Box 7, Folder 315)
    - Imperial War Museum, 1946 Sep 26 (Box 7, Folder 316)
    - Intercontinental Press, 1936-45, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 317)
    - "J" general, 1928-37 (Box 7, Folder 318)
    - Jonathan Cape Limited, 1926-63 (Box 7, Folder 319)
    - Jones, L. H.
    - Joseph, Michael
      See: Michael Joseph Ltd., Box 7, folder 330
    - "K" general, 1937-55 (Box 7, Folder 320)
    - "L" general, 1927-55 (Box 7, Folder 321)
    - Lane, Allen
      See: Penguin Books Limited, Box 8, folder 346
    - Latham, H. S.
      See: The MacMillan Company, Box 7, folder 324
    - Lilliput, 1937-38, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 322)
    - Lorant, Stefan
      See: Personal Correspondence, Box 3, folder 140; Lilliput, Box 7, folder 322; and Picture Post, Box 8, folder 347
    - Luker, N. G.
      See: The British Broadcasting Corporation, Box 7, folders 275-77
    - "M" general, 1936-62 (Box 7, Folder 323)
    - The MacMillan Company, 1925-26 (Box 7, Folder 324)
    - McMillan, John
      See: Great Britain: Foreign Office, Political Intelligence Department, Box 6, folder 307
    - Manchester Guardian, 1934-63, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 325-28)
    - Martin, Kingsley
      See: New Statesman, Box 7, folders 335-38
    - Methuen & Co. Ltd., 1933-38 (Box 7, Folder 329)
    - Michael Joseph Ltd., 1937-38 (Box 7, Folder 330)
    - Milford House, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 331)
    - Montague, L.
    - Morgan, J. A.
      See: New Statesman: Board of Directors, Correspondence, Box 7, folder 339
    - "Musso" Calendar, 1937-38 (Box 7, Folder 332)
    - "N" general, 1928-49, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 333)
    - National Liberal Club, 1937-63, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 334)
    - New Statesman
      - General correspondence, 1925-63 (Box 7, Folder 335-38)
      - Board of Directors
        - Correspondence, 1958-62 (Box 7, Folder 339)
        - Financial Reports, 1960-62 (Box 7, Folder 340)
        - Minutes, 1960-63 (Box 8, Folder 341)
        - Publisher's Reports, 1958-63 (Box 8, Folder 342)
    - Nielsen, Roger, 1958-63
      See: Hjemmet, Box 7, folder 312
    - "O" general, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 343)
    - Omar Khayyám Club, 1925-63 (Box 8, Folder 344)
    - "P" general, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 345)
    - Penguin Books Limited, 1937-45 (Box 8, Folder 346)
    - Picture Post, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 347)
    - "Pindar the Panda", 1939 (Box 8, Folder 348)
      See also: Published Drawings: Newspapers, "Pindar the Panda," Box 24, folders 1034-36
    - Punch, 1919-60, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 349)
    - "R" general, 1938-44 (Box 8, Folder 350)
    - Raphael Tuck & Sons, Limited
      See: "Musso" Calendar, Box 7, folder 332
    - Reynolds, Frank
    - Rhondda, Margaret, Lady
      See: Time and Tide, Box 8, folder 363
    - Roberts, John
    - Robertson, W. H.
    - Russell, Leonard, 1941-48 (Box 8, Folder 351)
    - "S" general, 1929-50 (Box 8, Folder 352)
    - Savage Club, 1927-37, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 353)
    - Scott Bader Commonwealth Limited, 1955-60 (Box 8, Folder 354)
    - Scott, Laurence P.
    - The Sette of Odd Volumes, 1928-38, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 355)
    - The Sketch, 1948-52 (Box 8, Folder 356)
    - Socialist Commentary, 1955-62 (Box 8, Folder 357)
    - Society of British Aircraft Constructors, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 358)
    - Soviet War News, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 359)
    - The Star
    - The Studio Ltd., 1937-38 (Box 8, Folder 360)
    - "T" general, 1922-56 (Box 8, Folder 361)
    - The Tatler, 1929-37 (Box 8, Folder 362)
    - Time and Tide, 1929-36 (Box 8, Folder 363)
    - Tiquet, Stanley
    - The Trades Union Congress General Council, 1933-46 (Box 8, Folder 364)
    - Tuck, Desmond A.
    - "U" general, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 365)
    - "V" general, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 366)
    - Victor Gollancz, Ltd., 1927-62 (Box 8, Folder 367)
      See also: Victor and Ruth Gollancz, Box 2, folder 82
    - Victoria & Albert Museum: Department of Engraving, Illustration & Design, 1937-44, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 368)
    - "W" general, 1929-56 (Box 8, Folder 369)
    - Wadsworth, A. P.
      See: Manchester Guardian, Box 7, folders 325-28 and Photographs of A. P. Wadsworth, Box 25, folder 1052
    - Wardell, Michael
    - Watt, W. P.
      See: "Pindar the Panda," Box 8, folder 348
    - William Heinemann, Ltd., 1929, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 370)
    - Winnington, Alan
      See: Communist Party of Great Britain, Box 6, folder 286
    - "Y" general, 1937-50 (Box 8, Folder 371)
    - Die Zukunft, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 372)
    - Unidentified, 1926-54, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 373)
  - SUBJECT
    - Contacts outside Great Britain
      - Abyssinia
        See: Ethiopia, Box 8, folder 409
      - Argentina, 1936 Sep 24 (Box 8, Folder 374)
      - Australia
        - "A" general, 1920-37, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 375)
        - "B" general, 1933-57 (Box 8, Folder 376)
        - "C" general, 1929-63 (Box 8, Folder 377)
        - "D" general, 1928-38 (Box 8, Folder 378)
        - "E" general, 1949 Jun 14 (Box 8, Folder 379)
        - "F" general, 1915-36 (Box 8, Folder 380)
        - "G" general, 1928-40 (Box 8, Folder 381)
        - "H" general, 1917-42 (Box 8, Folder 382)
        - "I" general, 1951 Jun 26 (Box 8, Folder 383)
        - "M" general, 1934-58 (Box 8, Folder 384)
        - "N" general, 1927, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 385)
        - "R" general, 1943-63 (Box 8, Folder 386)
        - "U" general, 1948 Aug 24 (Box 8, Folder 387)
        - "W" general, 1938-56 (Box 8, Folder 388)
        - Commonwealth National Library, 1945-52 (Box 8, Folder 389)
        - Dyason, J., 1938 (Box 8, Folder 390)
        - Evatt, Herbert, 1942-48 (Box 8, Folder 391)
        - Innes, Guy, 1934-48, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 392)
        - May, Clement, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 393)
        - McIntosh, Hugh D., 1928-41 (Box 8, Folder 394)
          See also: Sunday Times, Box 8, folder 398
        - Owen, Harrison, 1946-57 (Box 8, Folder 395)
        - Rayner, Fred, 1943-47, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 396)
        - Smith's Weekly, 1937, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 397)
        - Sunday Times, 1927-28 (Box 8, Folder 398)
        - The Sydney Morning Herald, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 399)
        - Unidentified, 1927-30 (Box 8, Folder 400)
      - Belgium, 1941-51 (Box 8, Folder 401)
      - Bulgaria, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 402)
      - Canada, 1934-57 (Box 8, Folder 403)
      - Ceylon
        See: Sri Lanka, Box 9, folder 439
      - China
        - General correspondence, 1942-43, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 404)
        - Chen, I-wan (Jack), part I, 1933-37 (Box 8, Folder 405)
          See also: Oversize, Box 36, folder 1207
      - Colombia, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 406)
      - Czechoslavakia, 1938-49, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 407)
      - Denmark, 1954-58 (Box 8, Folder 408)
      - Ethiopia, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 409)
      - France
        - General correspondence, 1934-47, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 410)
        - Paris-soir, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 411)
        - Saint-Jean, Robert de
          See: Paris-soir, Box 8, folder 411
      - Germany, 1930-58 (Box 8, Folder 412)
      - Greece, 1946-48 (Box 8, Folder 413)
      - Hungary, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 414)
      - India, 1937-55, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 415)
      - Ireland, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 416)
      - Israel, 1938-59, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 417)
      - Italy, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 418)
      - Japan
        - General correspondence, 1952-58 (Box 9, Folder 419)
        - Ishiyama, Motoharu
          See: Japan, Box 9, folder 419
        - Isobe, Juichiro
        - The Tokyo Shimbun
      - Jordan, 1955, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 420)
      - Kenya, 1933 Sep 26 (Box 9, Folder 421)
      - Korea, 1953 Jan 2 (Box 9, Folder 422)
      - Malta, 1947-58 (Box 9, Folder 423)
      - Mexico, 1939 Oct 11 (Box 9, Folder 424)
      - New Zealand
        - "A-N" general, 1936-63, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 425)
        - "P-W" general, 1928-57 (Box 9, Folder 426)
        - Campbell, R. M., 1937-55 (Box 9, Folder 427)
        - Christchurch Boys' High School, 1934-54 (Box 9, Folder 428)
        - City of Wellington Public Libraries, 1941-59 (Box 9, Folder 429)
        - Craddick, A. E., 1936-57 (Box 9, Folder 430)
        - Dunedin Public Library Association, 1955-57 (Box 9, Folder 431)
        - Fraser, Peter, 1940-49 (Box 9, Folder 432)
        - Jordan, William J., 1944-49, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 433)
        - Nash, Walter, 1937-63, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 434)
        - Otago Daily Times, 1945-48 (Box 9, Folder 435)
      - Palestine
        See: Israel, Box 9, folder 417
      - South Africa, 1938, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 436)
      - Spain
        - General correspondence, 1937-46 (Box 9, Folder 437)
        - Azcarate, Pablo de, 1938-45, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 438)
      - Sri Lanka, 1938-52 (Box 9, Folder 439)
      - Sweden, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 440)
      - Switzerland, 1932-61 (Box 9, Folder 441)
      - Syria, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 442)
      - U.S.S.R.